欢迎喜欢的朋友加入familyguy百度贴吧共同讨论
或加FG粉丝交流 QQ群 165859780
♪ It seems today that all you see ♪
♪ Is violence in movies and sex on TV ♪
♪ But where are those good old-fashioned values ♪
♪ On which we used to rely?
♪ Lucky there's a family guy
♪ Lucky there's a man who positively can do ♪
♪ All the things that make us
♪ Laugh and cry
♪ He's... a... Fam... ily... Guy! ♪
♪ Family Guy 10x13 ♪
Tom Tucker: The Man and His Dream
汤姆塔克:其人其梦
来自1988年的传记电影《Tucker:The Man and His Dream》
中文字幕: zurica 校对: wudixny 注释: wudixny
后期: zurica 压制: zurica @familyguy贴吧字幕组
晚上好 我是Tom Tucker
Good evening, I'm Tom Tucker,
我之所以戴上了口罩 是因为
and the reason I'm wearing this mask is because
今晚该演播室接待了一位来圆梦的孩子
we've got a Make-A-Wish kid in the studio tonight,
您在稍后的节目中将知晓
who, as you'll find out as the show goes on,
他是重度咳嗽患者
is quite a cougher.
本地新闻 West市长今日签署一项法案…
In local news, Mayor West signed a bill today...
看见了吗 我说的没错吧
See? That's-that's what I was talking about.
我们是现在就处理
Are we gonna get that,
还是等广告时间再弄
or are we gonna wait for commercial?
不 不 你得喷消毒剂
No, no, you have to spray it.
不能只擦两下…那好吧
You can't just wipe-- look, you know what?
咱们还是把这摄像机扔了吧
Let's just throw the whole camera out.
好的 Joyce 现在你来播
Okay, Joyce, you talk now.
我简直都不想开口了
I-I don't even want to open my mouth.
知道吗 Tom 我从没见过你戴口罩(面罩)
You know, Tom, I haven't seen you in a mask
自从你使用了艺名George P. Wilbur
since you went under the stage name George P. Wilbur.
美国职业替身演员 出演过多部恐怖片
呵呵呵 Joyce 你知道我们不谈这些
Oh-ho-ho, Joyce, you know we don't talk
尤其在直播的时候
about that on the air.
我的天啊
Oh, my God!
难道她…难道如她所说
Did she... did she just say
George P. Wilbur是Tom Tucker的艺名
that George P. Wilbur was Tom Tucker's stage name?
George P. Wilbur究竟是谁
Who the hell is George P. Wilbur?
就是在《万圣节4》中扮演杀人狂Michael Myers的家伙
That's the guy who played Michael Myers in Halloween 4,
他也在《万圣节6》中饰演该角色
那是有史以来最伟大的电影
the greatest movie of all time.
我看了那部电影不下一百遍
I've only seen that movie about a thousand times.
怎么会没注意到呢
How could I not have noticed that?
晚上好 我是Michael Myers
TOM: Good evening. I'm Michael Myers.
我有严重的精神问题
I have enormous psychological problems,
而且我要在你身上付诸实践了
and I'm going to take them out on you.
就是他 我都不敢相信
It is him. I can't believe it.
那可是我最喜欢的电影啊
I mean, that's, like, my favorite movie ever!
我还以为《摩登原始人之赌城万岁》
I thought The Flintstones in Viva Rock Vegas
由动画《摩登原始人》改编的电影(2000) 是1994年真人版电影的前传
是你最喜欢的电影
was your favorite movie.
不 那是我最喜欢的历史片
No, that's my favorite period piece.
嗯 还有《晚安 好运》
Well, that and Good Night and Good Luck.
乔治克鲁尼指导的电影(2005) 讲述美国传奇新闻人物Edward R. Murrow
虽然我被耍得提前退场了
Even though I was tricked into leaving early.
晚安 好运
Good night and good luck.
这是Murrow每次广播的结束语
也祝你晚安 好运 先生
And good night and good luck to you, sir.
嗨 Chris
Oh, hi, Chris.
在学校还好吗
How was school?
很好 我认识了一个女孩 妈妈
It was great. I met a girl, Mom!
很不错嘛 宝贝
That's wonderful, honey.
是啊 她名叫Lindsey 和州名一样
Yeah, her name is Lindsey, like the state.
她人好吗
Is she nice?
是的 她真的很好 超级可爱
Yeah, she's really nice and super pretty,
她的自行车座是草莓味的哦
and her bicycle seat smells like strawberries.
呃 好吧
Oh. Okay.
我要上楼去 调整一下心态
I'm gonna go upstairs and alternate between
从自杀式的悲观到希望式的狂喜
hopeful excitement and suicidal pessimism!
得给自己来点动力了
Got to get the energy up.
有了
Found it.
嗨 打扰一下 Tucker先生
Hey, uh, excuse me, Mr. Tucker.
你有空吗
You got a second?
哦 你好 Peter 当然 请进吧
Oh, hello, Peter. Sure, come on in.
谢了 呃 请听我说
Thanks. Um, hey, listen,
我刚刚发现你就是那个
I just found out that you were the guy
在《万圣节4》中扮演Michael Myers的人
who played Michael Myers in Halloween 4,
而我只想说
and I just want to say,
我认为那是有史以来
I think that was the most brilliant performance ever
最杰出的表演了
in the history of everything,
我斗胆请您在DVD上签个名
and I wanted to see if you would sign my DVD.
哦 我很乐意
Oh, I suppose.
谢谢 那后来发生了什么
Thanks. Hey, so, what happened?
为什么你不再拍电影了
How come you never did any more movies?
呃 我想在好莱坞闯出一番事业
Well, I tried to make a career out there in Hollywood,
可并没认识到演艺之路有多难
but I just didn't realize how tough acting is.
呵呵 你知道他们怎么说吗…
Well, you know what they say--
"拼搏牌杀癣灵"
"Tough actin' Tinactin."
杀真菌治脚气的药物 ^_^
要是那时知道就好了
I wish I'd known that then.
你看 《万圣节4》之后的生活
You see, life after Halloween 4
并不是一帆风顺
wasn't exactly smooth sailing.
自从我从那面罩后走出
Once I stepped out from behind that mask,
好莱坞就对我冷眼相待
Hollywood gave me the cold shoulder.
TOM：我能找到的活儿
TOM: The work I did manage to get
通常只是短时间的小角色
was usually just bit parts that didn't last too long.
比如在《考斯比一家》中扮演Denise的男友
Like the role of Denise's boyfriend on The Cosby Show.
NBC的黑人情景剧(1984-1992)
很高兴见到你 Martin
It's nice to meet you, Martin.
谢谢 Huxtable夫人
Thank you, Mrs. Huxtable.
那个 如果你们是一家子
So, if you guys are a family,
为什么所有人都黑的深浅不同
why are none of you the same shade of black?
多数时间我的头脑都沉浸在毒品中
I was also coked out of my skull most of the time.
不管怎么样 我没戏了
But whatever the case, I was done.
我离开了好莱坞 回到了家乡Quahog
I left Hollywood, moved back to my hometown of Quahog,
作为一个主持新人开始了紧张的工作
and wound up working here as a news anchor.
哇 可是 你不怀念吗
Wow. Well, don't you miss it?
无时无刻不想 可我不能再碰毒品了
Every second of every day, but I can't touch coke again.
它会毁掉我的生活
It would ruin my life.
不 我是说演出
No, I mean acting.
哦 当然
Oh. Of course.
可对我来说都结束了 过眼云烟
But it's over for me. That's all in the past.
呵呵 如果你找我 就能被打造成明星
Well, if you ask me, you got the makings of a star.
- 我要助你成功 - 嗯 不错的提议
- And I want to help you get there. - Well, that's a nice offer,
可我不太确定你为何要那样做
but I'm not quite sure how you expect to do that.
哦 这些年来你带给我了太多欢乐
Well, you've brought me so much joy over the years
饰演了那个可爱的少年杀手
as that lovable murderer of teenagers,
而我只是想回报你
and I want to return the favor.
我连经纪人都没有了
I don't even have an agent anymore.
那要不这样吧 我当你的经纪人
Well, then how about this? I'll be your agent.
你
You?
是的 我看过每一集《明星伙伴》
Yeah, I've seen every episode of Entourage.
HBO喜剧电视(2004- ) Chris的配音Seth Green曾客串
你所需要的只是一套假发
All you need is some fake hair
还有一群围着你转的霍比特人
and a bunch of Hobbits hanging around you.
五分钟后开始 Tucker先生
You're on in five minutes, Mr. Tucker.
你不属于这里
You don't belong here.
你该有更好的境遇
You're better than this.
像《万圣节4》这样更好的
You're Halloween 4 better.
听着 我感激你的建议
Look, I appreciate your offer,
可我在这里也干得非常出色
but I've got a pretty good thing going here.
几分钟后 我就要上镜头了
In a few minutes, I've got to be on camera
面对着800人
in front of 800 people.
晚上好 Quahog 我是Tom Tucker
Good evening, Quahog. I'm Tom Tucker.
今晚头条：罗德岛历史学会
Our top story tonight: The Rhode Island Historical Society
宣布已运抵一件铸铁身 橡木柄的
is heralding the arrival of a cast-iron, oak-handled
殖民时代被褥取暖器
Colonial bedsheet warmer,
此刻在州政府的圆形大厅中展出
now on display in the Statehouse Rotunda.
TOM：好的 就是这个
TOM: Okay, there it is.
就我个人理解 煤可以被装在其中
As I understand it, they would put the coal inside of that,
然后把这个物体放在被褥间
and then put the object between the sheets.
那个时代非常寒冷
It was very cold back then.
用它可以加热被褥
And it would warm the sheets.
我想主要内容就是这些了
And I-I think that's the gist of it.
这一段镜头还有多久
How much footage of this do we have?
哦 哦 是现场直播
Oh-oh, this is live.
那…她能听到我吗
This... Can-can she hear me?
好的 现在你可以放下它了
Okay, you can put it down now.
你…她不能听到我 好吧
You... She can't hear me. Okay.
那这究竟要做什么
What the hell is going on here?
那这…那这…是不是我脑子短路了
Is it... is it... Am I having a stroke?
慢着 Peter 留步
Wait, Peter! Don't go!
这么说 你改变主意了 是不是 老兄
So, you changed your mind, huh, buddy?
我们去好莱坞吧
We going to Hollywood?
当然了 不过我得说
You betcha. But I have to say,
我还以为你开着更炫的车呢
I thought you'd drive a fancier car.
什么 为啥
What? Why?
呃 你不是那个"Peter Griffin凯迪拉克"广告中的人吗
Well, aren't you the Peter Griffin of Peter Griffin Cadillac?
不 那是另一个人
No, that's another guy.
嗨 我是Peter Griffin
Hi. I'm Peter Griffin,
在Peter Griffin凯迪拉克 我们只信奉三件事:
and at Peter Griffin Cadillac, we believe in three things:
公平交易 家人 和友谊
fair dealing, family, and friendship.
我一辈子住在Quahog
I've lived in Quahog my whole life.
我喜欢这里
I love it here.
而你也会爱上Peter Griffin凯迪拉克
And you're gonna love a Peter Griffin Cadillac.
卑鄙小人
Scumbag.
好的 Lois 记得喂那只猫
All right, Lois, remember to feed the cat,
也要记得先养一只猫
and remember to get a cat.
我还是不太明白你为何非得
I still don't understand why you got to go
就要去好莱坞
all the way to Hollywood.
因为我知道Tom Tucker能成为伟大的演员
Because I know Tom Tucker could be a great actor,
我要帮助他成功
and I'm gonna help him make it happen.
你看 每个人都需要一个
You see, everybody needs just one person
慧眼识人的伯乐
to believe in their dreams
这样他们才能展翅高飞
so they can spread their wings and fly.
爸爸 我能不能花钱去上舞蹈班
Dad, can I have money for dance classes?
拉倒吧 你个矮胖的肉球
Sit down, you dumpy bread loaf.
我宁愿花钱看你不跳舞
I'd pay to see you not dance.
- 那你什么时候回来 - 我不知道
- When will you be back? - I don't know.
可我确定返乡之日
But I'll be sure to be back
肯定在Chris的高级舞蹈班单人演出之前
before Chris's big dance class recital.
我相信那个男孩
I believe in that boy.
可我不想跳舞
I don't want to dance!
你要跳舞
You'll dance!
哎呀 我不知道 Peter
Boy, I don't know, Peter,
回到这里让我有些紧张
being back out here makes me kind of nervous.
也许这就是个错误
Maybe-maybe this was all a mistake.
别傻了 Tom 你可是演员
Don't be silly, Tom-- you're an actor,
你就属于这里 现在 咱们拿上
and this is where you belong. Now, let's take some of
这些免费赠送的行李 出发吧
this complimentary luggage and get going.
呃 那我们怎么做呢
Well, so, h-how do we do this?
你什么也不用做
You do nothing.
你只用坐在一边 让你的经纪人
You just sit back and let your agent
敲开好莱坞的每一扇门 直到他
knock on every door in Hollywood till he gets
给你找来一份表演工作
you an acting job.
这就开始了
And that starts right now.
什么事 我能帮您吗
Yes? C-Can I help you?
不 可我能帮你
No, but I can help you.
你得雇用这个人
You need to hire this man.
呃 好吧
Oh. Um, okay.
你有没有任何装卸货物的经验
Well, do you have any experience handling bags?
啊 我懂了
Aha! I see!
典型的"潜规则"事务
Typical casting-couch stuff.
好的 孩子 你想不想
All right, kid, you want to make it
在娱乐圈飞黄腾达
in showbiz or don't you?
我还以为机场就是好莱坞
I thought the airport was Hollywood.
妈妈 我想让你见见我的新女友
Hey, Mom, I want you to meet my new girlfriend.
新女友
New girlfriend?
是的 你记得那个女孩吗
Yeah, you remember that girl
我跟你提过的Lindsey
Lindsey I told you about?
嗯 我约她出来 现在我们在交往了呢
Well, I asked her out, and now we are dating.
Lindsey 这是我妈妈 我的小弟弟Stewie
Lindsey, this is my mom, my little brother Stewie,
我的狗Brian
and my dog Brian.
嗨
Hey.
我的天呐
Oh, my God.
啧啧啧 看看你
My goodness, look at you.
你知道自己长得像谁吗
Do you even realize who you look like?
卡梅隆·迪亚兹 就是她
Cameron Diaz, that's who.
美国女演员 作品有《霹雳娇娃》等
你真是美艳惊人
You are gorgeous!
嗯 她太漂亮了…这我知道 妈妈
Well, she's awful pretty-- I know that, Mom.
太漂亮了！绝世美人！
Very pretty! Stunning!
你们在耍我吧
Are you kidding me?
你们都没察觉吗
Are they not seeing this?
我知道 是有点诡异 就好像
I know, it's kind of creepy. It's almost like
他是在和Lois恋爱 没错
he's dating Lois. Yeah.
看来某人有点俄狄甫斯情结
Looks like somebody's getting a little Oedipus-y.
即"恋母情结" 被故意读成了"偶滴pussy"
- 这么说合适吗 - 说了就说了
- Can we say that? - Just did.
好的 Tom 这招儿肯定管用
All right, Tom, this is totally gonna work.
好莱坞所有的大牌演员都在这儿就餐
All the biggest Hollywood players eat here,
我们只要让他们觉得我们是其中一员
and we just got to make them think we're one of them.
这就是为什么我戴上老式的好莱坞犹太眼镜
That's why I got these old Hollywood Jew glasses.
侍者 喂 侍者
Waiter! Oh, waiter!
来了 先生们要点菜吗
Yes sir. Are you gentlemen ready to order?
是的 我要点最贵最拉风的菜 而我这位客户
Yes, I will have the Big and Fancy, and my client here
要一瓶你们最好的牛排
will have a bottle of your best steak.
马上就好 先生
Right away, sir.
Peter 我不太清楚这些东西
Peter, I-I'm not sure what any of this
跟找到演出工作有什么关系
has to do with getting me acting jobs.
Tom 这里谁是经纪人
Tom, who's the agent here?
- 你 - 谁是演员
- You are. - And who is the actor?
呃 我
Well, I am.
- 等等 我是什么来着 - 经纪人
- Wait, which one am I again? - The agent.
- 那谁来给晚餐买单 - 我以为应该是你
- And who's paying for dinner? - I assumed you were.
哦 那我们最好把口袋里塞满面包
Ah, then we best load our pockets with bread
然后离开这个鬼地方
and get the hell out of here.
我们要走了
We have to go!
还不够贵
Not expensive enough!
借问一下 我情不自禁地注意到了你的眼镜
Excuse me, I couldn't help but notice your glasses,
你低劣的餐桌修养 还有你强烈的权利意识
your poor table manners and your huge sense of entitlement.
- 你是经纪人吗 - 我是
- Are you an agent? - I am.
你有十秒钟的时间来打动我 开始
You've got ten seconds to dazzle me. Go.
呵呵 我是NCIS的选角导演
Well, I'm the casting director for NCIS,
NBC的《海军罪案调查处》(2003- )
我们需要一位演员 明天拍摄时跑个龙套
and we need an actor for a small role that shoots tomorrow.
这就是你要找的人
This is your man.
太好了 他就像我们要找的人
That's great! He's got just the look we're after.
明天上午10点到这里来
Show up here at 10:00 a.m. tomorrow.
怎么样啊 Tom
How about that, huh, Tom?
你又重操旧业了
You're back in the business.
哇 Peter 我真不敢相信
Wow, Peter, I can't believe it!
哎 别那么吃惊嘛
Hey, don't be so surprised.
我已经为你踩平了道路 老兄
I've been pounding the pavement for you, buddy.
我甚至把所有的名片都发出去了
I even gave out all my business cards.
打我电话 打我电话 打我电话
Call me! Call me! Call me!
也许恶搞了魔术师Criss Angle
打我电话 打我电话 打我电话 打我电话
Call me! Call me! Call me! Call me!
啊 演艺圈
Ah, show business.
啊哈 是你们俩
Oh, hi, you two.
Lindsey 我想说 真是莫大的荣幸
You know, Lindsey, I just want to say how nice it is
能有这样一位漂亮小姐光临寒舍
to have such a beautiful young woman in our home.
哦 一个婴儿
Oh, a baby.
我有两次差点就生孩子了
I almost had one of you twice.
谁没经历过呢 呵呵
Who didn't, right?
那你们今晚去干什么
So, what are you two up to tonight?
其实我们还没定好
Well, we really haven't decided yet.
呃 我去想想做什么
Eh, I'll think of something while I'm taking
顺便在你父母卫生间里撇个大条
a chick dump in your parents' bathroom.
那我替你拿着包包吧
And I will hold your purse.
Chris真走运
Good for Chris, huh?
他泡上了一个正妹 有木有
He picked a peach, didn't he?
Lois 你不觉得自己喜欢Lindsey 某种程度上是因为
Lois, don't you think maybe part of the reason you like Lindsey
她长得太像你了
could be because she looks so much like you?
什么
What?
你在说什么？
What are you talking about?
不是吗 她明显是个很差劲的人
Come on, she's clearly an awful person.
我想可能是虚荣心作祟
And I think it's possible that your vanity
使你有点无视了这一切
has made you a little blind to that.
哦…我明白是怎么回事了…你嫉妒了
Oh... I see what's going on here-- you're jealous.
Chris有佳人相伴
Chris has a wonderful young woman in his life,
而你什么都没有
and you've got nothing.
她说的不无道理 Brian
She's kind of right, Brian.
你所有的只不过是破旧的绳索玩具
All you've got is a worn-out rope toy
上次有只松鼠路过时还嘲笑你
and that squirrel who comes by once a day to taunt you.
喂
Hey!
哎 快离开这儿 这是我家院子
Hey, get out of here! This is our yard!
你不属于这儿 什么东西都别碰
You don't belong there! Don't you touch anything!
我昨天都跟你说过了
I told you all this yesterday!
庆祝你第一次重要的电视演出
To your first big TV acting job.
现在我们回到NCIS
MALE TV ANNOUNCER: We now return to NCIS.
哦 就是这段 我的戏份
Oh, here it is. Here comes my part.
打扰一下
Excuse me.
我在找Ed Manzelli
I'm looking for Ed Manzelli.
晚上好 我就是Ed Manzelli
Good evening. I'm Ed Manzelli.
我能为您做什么
What can I do for you?
我找一个曾在这里工作的人
I'm looking for a guy who used to work here.
名叫Mario 你知道他去了哪里吗
Name's Mario. Got any idea where he could be?
我已经一个多月没见到他了
I haven't seen him in over a month.
我的台词结束了
That's the end of my line.
该你了 NCIS
Your line, NCIS.
你这家伙呀 又让我找回那感觉了
You son of a bitch, you made me feel again.
哦 你别这样 我也有感触
Oh, don't you go 'cause I'll go.
Peter啊 我真想好好谢你
You know, Peter, I just want to thank you
为你对我的付出
for all you've done for me.
你…你真是顶级的经纪人
You... You are one hell of an agent.
呵呵 有你这样的客户 举手之劳
Well, with you as a client, it's easy.
Griffin先生
WOMAN: Mr. Griffin?
- 什么事 Sandra - 你有个秘书
- Yes, Sandra? - You have a secretary?
她自称为助理 不过还是秘书
She calls herself an assistant, but yes.
什么事 Sandra
What is it, Sandra?
有位先生想见您
There's a man here to see you.
他说想谈谈请您当经纪人的事宜
He says he wants to talk to you about being his agent.
真的 那好 赶紧让他进来吧
Really?! Well, then, by all means, send him in!
嗨 基友们
Hey, knucklebutts!
BOTH: James Woods?!
可我…我不明白
But I... I don't understand!
我…我还以为你死了
I... I thought you were dead!
呵呵…我没死
Well... I'm not.
我不相信你
I don't believe you.
上帝 是真的吗
God, is that true?
上帝
God?
上帝 你在吗
God, are you there?
别啊 不许打手枪 你可是上帝
Come on, don't touch yourself. You're God.
我不明白 上次我们见到你
I-I don't get it. Last time we saw you,
Diane Simmons在你背后捅了一刀
Diane Simmons had just stabbed you in the back with a knife.
S09E01的剧情
是的 你到底是怎样死而复生的
Yeah! How the hell did you come back to life?!
呵呵 先生们
Well, gentlemen,
成为好莱坞大明星确实有它的好处
sometimes being a big Hollywood star has its advantages.
咦 这是个大人物吗
Hey, is this guy somebody?
没错 那是James Woods
Yeah, that's James Woods!
我们这儿有个名人
We got a celebrity here!
重复一遍 这不是普通死者
I repeat, this is not a normal dead person!
这是名人
This is a celebrity!
JAMES：成为著名电影演员使我有权
JAMES: Being a famous movie star entitled me
接受最顶尖的医疗服务
to topnotch medical care
而社会上的其他人则无法享受
not available to the rest of society.
我的身体被立即送进好莱坞医院
My body was immediately taken to a Hollywood hospital,
连接上了一个17岁的稚嫩少女
where I was hooked up to a 17-year-old ingenue.
根据好莱坞的法律
And in accordance with Hollywood law,
她的生命力被注入了我体内
her life force was infused into me,
使我起死回生
bringing me back from the dead.
TOM：那个女孩最后怎样了
TOM: What happened to the girl?
JAMES：我把她从车窗扔到了Nora Ephron身上
JAMES: I threw her out a car window at Nora Ephron.
美国导演和编剧 作品有《西雅图夜未眠》等
别再把杰克·尼克尔森塑造成娘娘腔了
Stop making Jack Nicholson a pansy!
两人合作过《心火》1986
你说的是Nancy Meyers吧
You're thinking of Nancy Meyers!
女导演 作品有《天生一对》等 与Jack合作过《爱是妥协》
你也一样
You're the same thing!
哇 太神奇了
Wow. That's amazing.
那你怎么说 Peter 愿意做我的经纪人吗
So, what do you say, Peter? Will you be my agent?
我不懂了 为什么你这样的大牌
I don't get it. Why would a big shot
要找我做经纪人
like you want me for an agent?
因为你积极进取 因为你有渴望
Because you're an up-and-comer, because you're hungry.
我是挺饿的
I am hungry.
可你给让我们全家
But you put me and my family
这几年不得安生
through a lot of crap over the years.
他冒充过Peter(S06E09) 毁了Brian的电视剧(S08E15) 等等
我为什么要帮助你
Why would I want to help you?
因为你是我经纪人
Well, because you're my agent.
哦 天啊 你说得对 我的确是
Oh, my God, you're right! I am!
哎 这就打住吧
Hey, hold on now.
你来这儿是当我的经纪人
You came out here to be my agent.
Tom 别紧张 你们两个我都能搞得定
Tom, relax, I can take care of you both.
只怕你们还没见识到我的能耐吧
You'd be surprised how much I can handle.
Peter 你把Stewie送到幼儿园
Peter, I need you to drop Stewie off at day care,
再把这一大摞旧的银行对账单粉碎销毁
and then shred this big stack of old bank statements.
你就放心吧 Lois
You got it, Lois.
他总是这么安静吗
Is he always this quiet?
Kevin昨晚试图自杀
So, Kevin made another attempt on his life last night.
他喝了两瓶洗洁精
He drank two bottles of dish soap.
呵呵 我们家也有新闻
Well, we have some news, too.
Chris和一个相当漂亮的女生在谈恋爱
Chris is dating the most wonderful girl.
你看 每个人都说 "怀孕期间别抽烟"
You know, everyone said, "Don't smoke during your pregnancy,"
可我看那副作用在他身上也消失了 现在他挺有型的
but I think some of it rubbed off on him 'cause now he's cool.
那就好
That's nice.
我得走了 Lois
Well, I should go, Lois.
嗯 我差不多也该走了
Yeah, I should probably get going myself.
我的天呐
Oh, my God!
怎么了 什么事 Lois
What? What is it, Lois?
那个女孩…
That girl over there--
那…那就是Chris的女友
that... that's Chris's girlfriend!
哎 其实 她长得有点像你呢 Lois
Hey, you know, she kind of looks like you, Lois.
说不定她会感激我请你喝咖啡呢
Maybe she'll thank me for buying the coffee.
你也觉得她像我吗
You think she looks like me, too?
天啊
Oh, my God.
我开始觉得Brian是对的
I'm starting to think Brian was right.
也许我因为自己愚蠢的虚荣而变得盲目
Maybe I have been blinded by my own stupid vanity.
那个女孩除了麻烦一无是处
That girl is nothing but trouble.
你要告诉Chris吗
Are you gonna tell Chris?
看来不得不那么做
I guess I'll have to,
可他对坏消息的承受力不好
but he doesn't take bad news very well.
Chris 宝贝 我很遗憾地告诉你
Oh, Chris, honey, I'm so sorry to tell you this,
你爷爷去世了
but your grandfather died.
恶搞了《侏罗纪公园》里的双脊龙
好的 先生们
All right, gentlemen.
你们为我的客户带来了什么
So, what do you got for my client?
我们正在制作一部中等成本的动作片
Well, we're making a mediocre action film,
我们认为James是合适的人选
and we think James is just the guy to do a serviceable job
能出色地完成表演任务 而Jeremy Irons Jeff Goldblum
in a supporting role that Jeremy Irons, Jeff Goldblum,
和Craig T. Nelson都无法胜任
and Craig T. Nelson have already passed on.
这几人包括James Woods都是60岁以上的老戏骨
好吧 我们要先看看剧本
Well, we'd need to see a script first.
嗯 看起来不错
Oh, looks good.
你觉得呢 James
What do you think, James?
- 我喜欢 - 很好
- I like it. - Good.
我说咱们就接了吧
I say we move on this.
好的 那就谈条件吧
All right, then, let's negotiate.
- 我们什么都要 - 我们什么都不给
- We want everything. - We'll give you nothing.
- 我们要一部分 - 成交
- We want something. - Deal.
呃 竟然又是这个罗德岛的乡巴佬
Ugh, not this hillbilly from Rhode Island again.
见鬼去吧
No thank you.
我是Peter Griffin 知名经纪人
This is Peter Griffin, famous agent,
不过你可以叫我PG十三叔
but you can call me PG-13.
指影片分级为13岁以下父母指导观看 也是Peter名字的缩写
Ba-boom!
请留言
Leave a message.
嗨 Peter 我是Tom
Hi, Peter, it's Tom.
呃 只是想再联系你一下
Uh, just trying to reach you again.
你知道 关于那次会面
And you know, about that meeting
你安排我去见Heath Ledger…
you set up with me and Heath Ledger...
演出过《蝙蝠侠前传2》《断臂山》等 于2008年去世
他…他根本没出现
He... He never showed.
也许我走错了熊猫快餐店 可我…
Maybe I was at the wrong Panda Express, but I...
美国连锁中餐馆
不管怎样 给我回个电话
Anyway, uh, call me back.
呵呵 谢谢你邀请我来吃午饭 Peter
Hey, listen, thanks for inviting me to lunch, Peter.
我开始还有些紧张
I-I was starting to get nervous
当你不回我电话的时候
when you weren't returning my calls.
Tom 我…我不知道该怎么跟你说
Tom, I... I didn't know how to say this to you,
所以 给你拿着这张纸
so, here, take this piece of paper.
你准备播音 四 三 二…
And you're on in four, three, two...
"Peter Griffin放弃了Tom Tucker这个客户"
"Peter Griffin drops Tom Tucker as a client."
你…你放弃我了吗
You're-you're dropping me as a client?
是的 刚在新闻里听到了吧
Yeah, just heard it on the news.
你怎么能这样做
How could you do this?!
听着 现在的情形完全不同了
Look, it's a whole different landscape
从周二开始
out here since Thursday.
现在一切都在电脑上
Everything's on computers now.
Peter 我放弃了极好的工作来干这个
Peter, I left a very good job for this!
你是我来这里的唯一原因
You're the only reason I came back out here!
我很想帮你 Tom
I wish I could help you, Tom,
可这是上层的决定
but this is coming from upstairs.
空手道馆吗
The karate studio?
Tom 我得走了
Tom, I have to go now.
可如果你要成了Kevin James 就打我电话吧
But if you're ever Kevin James, I want you to give me a call.
喜剧演员 演出过《动物园看守》等
喂
Mm. Hello?
Peter 是我 小伍 帮我个忙
Peter, it's me, Woodsy! I need a favor.
什么啊 现在是夜里两点
What?! It's, like, 2:00 a.m.
是的 听好了 我正在马尔蒙庄园旅馆
Yeah, so listen, I'm at Chateau Marmont,
我刚认识了一个18岁的女孩
I just met this 18-year-old chick,
我在想要不要带她回家
and I can't decide whether to take her home
还是继续跟Tom Sizemore一起嗑药
or keep doing blow with Tom Sizemore
演出过《黑鹰坠落》《珍珠港》等
看看我今晚还能不能表现得更好一些
and see if I can do better later in the night.
呃 那好…
Well, okay, um...
你 你喜欢她么
Do, uh, do-do you love her?
什么 你看 我把她的照片发给你
What?! Look, I'm texting you her picture.
跟我说说 你觉得她够正吗
Just tell me if you think she's hot enough.
我…这是什么照片
I... What is this a picture of?
这是冬瓜的底部吗
Is that the bottom of a white pumpkin?
她正不正点
Is she hot or not?
- 差不多吧 - 很好 很好
- I-I guess. - Okay, good, great.
那你赶紧整理公寓 我们15分钟后到
So clear out of your apartment; we're gonna be there in 15.
什么 我还在睡觉呢
What?! I'm sleeping.
为什么你不能带她去你家
Why can't you bring her to your place?
这事不能说太细 老兄
I don't know, man.
她是我表妹 感觉怪怪的
It's my aunt's daughter. It's weird.
Chris 宝贝
Chris, honey,
有件事我想跟你谈谈
there's something I want to talk to you about.
当然可以 妈妈 请进吧
Why, sure, Mom. Come on in.
Chris 你的那个女朋友 Lindsey
Chris, you know your girlfriend, Lindsey?
嗯
Yeah.
呃 宝贝
Well, honey,
我看见他和别的男生亲热
I saw her making out with another boy.
她是用上面的嘴亲热 还是用下面的嘴亲热
Was she kissing with her mouth, or her pants-mouth?
这两样她都做
Because she does both.
Chris 我不敢相信你都知道这些
Chris, I can't believe you knew about this!
太可怕了
That's terrible!
为什么你要和这样的女生谈恋爱
Why would you even date a girl like that?
呃 因为…我以为她会像你
Well, because... I-I thought she'd be like you.
像我
Like me?
呵呵 你得承认 妈妈
Well, you got to admit, Mom,
她确实长得很像你
she does look a lot like you.
我是说 我只是参照了你和爸爸 明白吗
I mean, I just look at you and Dad, you know?
他就是个人间杯具 而你还能忍让他
He's a complete train wreck, and you put up with him.
我自己也一无是处
And I'm no prize myself.
所以我想 如果不找一个像你的女孩
So, I guess I figured if I don't find a girl just like you,
我可能永远没有归宿
I might never find anyone.
噢 Chris
Oh, Chris.
你当然能找到归宿
Of course you'll find someone.
你也有自己的价值
And you are a prize.
你是一个帅气的 善良的年轻人
You're a handsome, kind-hearted, young man,
不管哪个女孩拥有了你 都是她的福气
and any girl would be lucky to have you in her life.
你真的这么想
You really think so?
当然了 亲爱的
Of course I do, sweetheart.
谢谢 妈妈
Thanks, Mo
我这就把电脑上的"花季护航"软件关掉
Now I'm gonna take the child filter off the computer,
祝你度过一个愉快的夜晚
and I want you to have a fun night.
好的 就是这个 James
Okay, this is it, James.
我弄好了你的下一份演出方案
I got your next project right here.
Peter 你为我策划了许多方案
Peter, you've pitched me dozens of projects,
可全部是跟饰演"干草车出游"的司机有关
and all of them involve me playing a hayride driver.
起源于堪萨斯乡间的民俗活动
我没注意啊 我只是看你那么做
I don't know, I just see you doing that.
这一年 全演吸血鬼 下一年 全演干草车司机
You know, this year, it's vampires, next year, it's hay.
这些事交替循环
These things go in cycles.
Peter 这应该是解雇你的好时机
Peter, this is probably a good time to fire you.
什么
What?!
不会吧 Peter 你以为咱俩谁在开玩笑
Come on, Peter, who are we kidding?
你只是一个人在运作
You're a one-man operation.
你了解我 我需要完整的团队
You know me. I need a whole crew.
我需要管嗑药的人 管泡妞的人 管健身的人
I need a drugs guy, a girls guy, a fitness guy,
一个开船的人 能把东西远远地扔在某处
a guy with a boat who can dump stuff way-out-there kind of guy.
抛尸么 O(∩_∩)O~
可…可你是我唯一的客户
But... But you're my only client!
没有你 我就废了
Without you, I'm ruined!
呵呵 这就是演艺圈
Well, that's show business.
如果你不介意的话 我要接个假电话
Now, if you'll excuse me, I have to answer this fake phone call.
喂 麦当劳的Grimace
Hello? Grimace from McDonald's?
抱歉 Peter 我得处理下这事
Sorry, Peter, I got to take this.
没关系 我理解
No, I understand.
嗨 Tom
Hey, Tom.
你还好吗
How you doing?
你想做什么
What do you want?
James Woods炒了我
James Woods fired me.
听着 我想过了
Listen, I-I been thinking.
我真的很对不住你
I was a real jerk to you.
我把你拉到这儿来
I dragged you out here,
却在你最需要我时 抛弃了你
only to dump you when you needed me the most.
我想要说的就是
I guess what I'm saying is,
我真的为这一切感到抱歉
I'm really sorry about everything.
不是一句抱歉就完了 Peter
Sorry doesn't cut it, Peter.
我辞掉了工作 舍弃了一切来到这儿
I quit my job, I left everything behind to come out here.
我知道 可我只是想帮个忙
I know, but I was just trying to help.
我从没想过要害你
I never wanted to let you down.
好吧 我想你唯一的罪过就是信任我
Well, I suppose your only crime is that you believed in me.
然后又很突然地不再信任我
And then stopped believing in me rather abruptly.
那你怎么说
So what do you say?
准备一起回故乡吗
You ready to go back to where we both belong?
好吧 咱们回家去
Yup. Let's go home.
真好
Sounds good.
哎 你看看James Woods发给我的这张照片
Hey, check out this picture James Woods texted me.
这是什么 漏了气的气球吗
What is that? A balloon running out of air?
呵呵 我还指望你能解答呢
Yeah, see, I was hoping you would know.
这是他表妹的菊花
It's his cousin's anus.
晚上好 Quahog 我是Tom Tucker
Good evening, Quahog. I'm Tom Tucker.
我是Joyce Kinney
And I'm Joyce Kinney.
Tom 我想代表五频道新闻的所有同事说
Tom, I think I speak for all of us here at Channel Five News
很高兴你能回到这里
when I say it's good to have you back here
拿着你原先一半的薪水
at half your original salary.
还是你的两倍 Joyce
Still twice yours, Joyce.
今晚头条:
Our top story tonight:
Quahog第一家有机超市于本周末开张
Quahog's first organic supermarket opens this weekend.
所以赶紧去吧 别等基佬把那儿
So head on down before the gays turn it
变成了游乐场所 就像巴诺书店
into a cruising ground like they did the Barnes and Noble
美国最大的零售连锁书店
楼上的咖啡厅 最后只能关门大吉
upstairs coffee bar, which they had to close.
嗯 我真高兴Tom又找回了工作
Well, I'm just happy Tom got his job back.
可是很遗憾错过了你的女朋友 Chris
But I'm sorry I missed meeting your girlfriend, Chris.
没关系 老爸
That's okay, Dad.
对了 Chris 我还没问你
Yeah, Chris, I never asked you.
你和她分手的时候 Lindsey说了什么
What did Lindsey say when you broke up with her?
哦 看起来她并不在乎
Oh, she didn't seem to mind.
我觉得她早就移情别恋了
I think she already moved on to someone else.
谢谢你给我买的这些衣服 Glenn
Thanks for buying me these clothes, Glenn.
别客气
You're welcome.
你被解雇了
And you're dismissed.
我还能留着那20美元吗
Do I still get to keep the 20?
深切悼念Ricky Garduon
Family Guy的一位分镜师
中文字幕: zurica 校对: wudixny 注释: wudixny
后期: zurica 压制: zurica @familyguy贴吧字幕组